<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Links-files on Examplelab</title>
    <link>https://www.examplelab.com.ar/links-files/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Links-files on Examplelab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.examplelab.com.ar/links-files/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.examplelab.com.ar/links-files/87/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.examplelab.com.ar/links-files/87/</guid>
      <description>Write Code Like You Just Learned How to Program  Artículo extraído desde: https://prog21.dadgum.com/87.html  I&amp;rsquo;m reading Do More Faster, which is more than a bit of an advertisement for the TechStars start-up incubator, but it&amp;rsquo;s a good read nonetheless. What struck me is that several of the people who went through the program, successfully enough to at least get initial funding, didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to program. They learned it so they could implement their start-up ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.examplelab.com.ar/links-files/all-time-learning-to-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.examplelab.com.ar/links-files/all-time-learning-to-program/</guid>
      <description>This is Why You Spent All that Time Learning to Program There&amp;rsquo;s a standard format for local TV news broadcasts that&amp;rsquo;s easy to criticize. (By &amp;ldquo;local,&amp;rdquo; I mean any American town large enough to have its own television station.)
There&amp;rsquo;s an initial shock-value teaser to keep you watching. News stories are read in a dramatic, sensationalist fashion by attractive people who fill most of the screen. There&amp;rsquo;s an inset image over the shoulder of the reader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.examplelab.com.ar/links-files/disparar-y-avanzar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.examplelab.com.ar/links-files/disparar-y-avanzar/</guid>
      <description>Disparar y avanzar From The Joel on Software Translation Project Artículo original: Fire And Motion
Hay veces en las que no me sale nada.
Fijo. Llego a la oficina, doy un par de vueltas, veo si hay correo cada diez segundos, navego por la red y tal vez haga algunas tareas tontas como pagar la factura de la American Express. Pero lo de volver a escribir código con fluidez no ocurre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.examplelab.com.ar/links-files/iam-boring-programmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.examplelab.com.ar/links-files/iam-boring-programmer/</guid>
      <description>I’m a boring programmer (and proud of it) I have a confession to make — I’m not a rock star programmer. Nor am I a hacker. I don’t know ninjutsu. Nobody has ever called me a wizard.
Still, I take pride in the fact that I’m a good, solid programmer. One who works hard at his craft and really enjoys it, even without the fancy labels.
Yet every week I see a call for ninja programmers, who I assume slice lines of code with incredible precision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.examplelab.com.ar/links-files/own-the-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.examplelab.com.ar/links-files/own-the-tools/</guid>
      <description>Own the Tools  Artículo extraído desde: https://www.raptitude.com/2020/12/own-the-tools  When I need to look up a word, most of the time I do it in a paper dictionary.
I’m pretty quick at flipping to the right place, and I try to get quicker each time. However, it will never be as quick as typing the word into Google.
My switch back to paper wasn’t motivated by cantankerousness. It wasn’t a romantic thing or a hipster thing, or an “I love the smell of books” thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.examplelab.com.ar/links-files/programmings-dirtiest-little-secret/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.examplelab.com.ar/links-files/programmings-dirtiest-little-secret/</guid>
      <description>Programming&amp;rsquo;s Dirtiest Little Secret  Archivo descargado desde: steve-yegge.blogspot.com  This is another one I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to write forever. Man, I&amp;rsquo;ve tried a bunch of times. No ruck. Not Rucky. Once again I&amp;rsquo;m stuck feeling so strongly about something that I&amp;rsquo;m tripping over myself trying to get my point across.
So! Only one thing left to try: bust open a bottle of wine and see if that gets the ol&#39; creative juices flowing all over my keyboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.examplelab.com.ar/links-files/traducciones/own-the-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.examplelab.com.ar/links-files/traducciones/own-the-tools/</guid>
      <description>Se dueño de las herramientas  Artículo extraído desde:  https://www.raptitude.com/2020/12/own-the-tools   Traducción por Hugo Ruscitti  Cuando necesito consultar una palabra, casi siempre lo hago en un diccionario de papel.
Soy muy rápido buscando la página exacta, y trato que volverme cada vez más rápido con la práctica. De todas formas, nunca va a ser más rápido que escribir la palabra en Google.
Usar un diccionario físico no es de cascarrabias.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
